<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on GSoC 24 weekly blogs</title>
    <link>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on GSoC 24 weekly blogs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:01:59 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week4</title>
      <link>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/week4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:01:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/week4/</guid>
      <description> Worked on solving the discrepancy in the _eval_as_leading_term and _eval_as_nseries method of the singularity function for its discrepancy for non-negative arguments. The solution involves declaring a new a function in the beams module that mimics and will replace all limits calls in beams.py as otherwise there could be a possibility of an infinite recursion.issue </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week3</title>
      <link>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/week3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 08:08:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/week3/</guid>
      <description> Started work on implementation of a method to return limits results in terms of a piecewise function to better satisfy routines in gruntz that require sign of terms, and will be raising a PR for the same soon. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week2</title>
      <link>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/week2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 10:03:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/week2/</guid>
      <description> Worked on removing unnecessary nsimplify terms from the codebase through the following PR Removed unnecessary codeblock in gruntz pertaining to mrv calculations for pow type expressions.PR </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week1</title>
      <link>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/week1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 12:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/week1/</guid>
      <description> Solved the issue pertaining to nseries method of the abs class in the PR </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 20:29:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://arnabnandikgp.github.io/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to the weekly blogpost for my GSoC 2024 project. My proposal for Improving series expansions and limit computations for the Sympy has been accepted for GSoC 2024. For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know about Sympy,Sympy is a Python library for symbolic mathematics. It aims to become a full-featured computer algebra system (CAS) while keeping the code as simple as possible in order to be comprehensible and easily extensible.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
